Yes! Hit him!
Hit him again! Kill him!
- Kill that son of a bitch!
- Uh, do you wanna just...
Yeah! Break... his... face!
Come on! Come on!
Watch the back of your head.
You need to play harder boy,
you hear me?
You need to play harder!
So... you must hit
a lot of guys, huh?
Well, I'm a cop, so it comes
with the job sometimes.
It's only ever self...
That is so hot. I would
love to see you hit someone.
Oh. Uh... maybe.
Yes!
All right, let's fight, let's go.
Charlotte Mitchell was her name.
She was a book writer
writing a book.
Got control of the crime scene.
It's gonna be a wide suspect list.
Get statements from all the security
guards, vendors, and attendants.
Find out who could get backstage.
Right. It's gonna be
hundreds, at least.
Look, uh, just to be clear,
I don't own this arena.
I simply promoted the fight.
I have no liability here.
What was Charlotte
Mitchell's connection to you?
She was writing a book
about this fight
about my guy, Manny Flacco,
and Rowdy Merriman.
She said it was a...
Microcosm of whatever. I...
I figured any P.R.
for my boy Manny is good P.R.
That's the kind of kid he is.
Got the initial report from the M.E...
Shot twice close range.
Had a purse, money, jewelry all intact.
Estimated time of death...
8:30, 9:00 P.M.
That was right in the middle
of the fight.
Excuse me.
When was the last
time you saw Ms. Mitchell?
We were supposed to sit
together during the fight.
She didn't show up.
Sir...
Why are you staring
at me like that?
I was staring?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
My mind was elsewhere.
That's Charlotte Mitchell, right?
And you're, uh...
And you're Leonard Artash, promoter.
- Let's go talk to the fighters, shall we?
- Really?
Well, Rigsby just told us
it wasn't a robbery.
We know it wasn't sexual.
Looks like it was in cold blood,
so not a crime of passion.
What's that leave us?
I'd bet your pension
this has something
to do with the fight.
But Manny and Merriman were
in the cage when she was shot.
- Are you a detective?
- No.
Well, then.
Manny Flacco, you're the man.
You were fantastic in there.
Messed him up like
he was dog meat.
You're gonna be champion
of the world. You hear me?
Champion of the world.
- You gotta deal with this now?
- Yes, ma'am, we do.
What's the problem, Bea?
Who are those guys?
They're cops.
Oh, come on now. Can it wait?
Let the kid enjoy his win.
Talk to him after he checks
in with the doctor.
- I don't need the doc.
- Hey, better safe than sorry, right?
Manny's got nothing
to do with this.
Nothing to do with what?
Charlotte Mitchell was
murdered earlier this evening.
- Charlotte murdered? Oh, my God.
- Stay cool. Don't get excited.
She was found shot to death
in a service corridor
underneath the arena.
Happened during your fight.
- You knew and you didn't tell me?
- Manny, come on.
You know we're trying to protect you.
Listen, I didn't wanna
spoil your night.
- Who did this?
- That's what we're looking to find out.
You liked her a lot, huh?
This lady, uh, what's her name?
- "What's her name"
- Charlotte Mitchell.
Yeah, I liked her.
Everybody liked her.
She was good people.
Yeah, she was.
Okay.
Great.
Well, thank you.
- Uh, where's Merriman's room?
- Oh. So we're done now, are we?
- Oh, I'm sorry. You have some questions.
- Yeah.
She has some questions.
You don't wanna go back there.
These aren't the droids
you're looking for.
Tough night, huh?
Uh... listen. Consolation-wise
you know what Nietzsche said.
Man, who the hell are you?!
You know what?
I don't even care.
Get your butt outta here!
- I'm CBI. I'm investigating a murder.
- Oh, you're a cop?
- Well, not officially.
- No, man, screw murder.
I got a robbery to report.
That little fanny-pack Flacco
wouldn't have won dip
if he didn't have the
stinkin' ref in his pocket!
Son of a bitch was head-buttin'
me the whole night!
Ouch.
- Who got murdered?
- Charlotte Mitchell.
No kiddin'? The book writer?
Damn. That's messed up.
Ain't gonna be no book now,
I guess.
They rape her as well?
She was kinda hot.
Hello?
Either you're a genius manipulator
concealing your complicity in the case
or you're a... dimly lit clown.
Which is it?
Get back over here
- You were right, big man.
- Say that again, you son of a bitch!
Why don't you get back here
see what one of your mouths can...
Hey! Hey!
Leave him alone! He's a cop!
I'll get back to you.
Ballistics came back.
9-millimeter weapon.
Rifling patterns and striations
on the bullets
indicate the gun used to kill
Charlotte Mitchell
was also used in a murder
back in 2001.
The weapon was never recovered.
The killer was a man
named Joe Reyes.
Got out eight months ago.
Early release.
Cho's still working through
suspects from the arena.
Take Rigsby and talk to Reyes.
Find out what happened
to that gun.
- I'm gonna go talk to the victim's father.
- Rigsby's... busy.
With what?
- Mr. LaRoche is interviewing him.
- Oh?
A man named Todd Johnson
was murdered while in CBI custody.
Yes. Cop killer,
burned to death in his cell.
I just wanted to get your opinion
on some things.
You were an arson investigator
before coming to CBI, right?
- Yeah, in San Diego.
- Yeah. Are you familiar with...
- Pyrophoric igniters?
- Sure. Liquid or solid?
Used in conjunction
with a xylene accelerant?
- Overkill, I'd say.
- Really?
And the fire safety system
here in CBI...
Easy to access and deactivate?
Top-of-the-line E.S.F.R system?
No.
Bypassing that took real know-how.
You could deactivate it,
couldn't you?
Yes, I could.
Are you accusing me?
Are you confessing?
Your father
is Steven Robert Rigsby.
Yes, he is.
What does he got to do
with the investigation?
Used to be affiliated with the Iron Gods
motorcycle gang, yes?
Well, you know he was.
Yes, I have his sheet here.
Robbery.
Narcotics.
Assault.
Manslaughter. Quite the rascal.
Look, I have nothing to do
with my father.
Nothing at all?
No card at Christmas?
Nope. We don't talk.
I don't know where he is.
LaRoche.
You're supposed to inform me
when you talk to one of my people.
That's not a right.
That's a courtesy we extend
on occasion.
Well, in the future I'd like you
to extend that courtesy to me.
Thank you, agent Rigsby.
That should do it.
"Shall he lead"
"Every foe is vanquished"
"And Christ is lord indeed"
- Amen, amen.
- Amen.
Welcome. We have newcomers,
brothers and sisters.
Make 'em feel welcome.
Joseph Reyes?
My gun. A woman
was killed with my gun?
Same one you used back in 2001.
So you just cannot escape
the sins of the past.
All you can do is ask the lord's guidance
and you know, keep on, man.
- Did you know Charlotte Mitchell?
- No, ma'am, I did not
and I don't have that gun
anymore either.
Got rid of it back
when you shot that guy?
What did you do with it?
I gave it to a lady friend
of mine at the time.
- What did she do with it?
- That I don't know.
I haven't seen her since my arrest.
What was the lady's name?
Uh... Dawn. Dawn May.
- Address?
- Don't know.
Like I said, I didn't look for her
when I got out.
After finding my faith, I realize I had
to turn my back on all my evil ways
and all the people that could possibly
lead me back there.
All right. Thanks for your time.
Why did you kill that man
back in 2001?
If you don't mind my asking.
I don't know, ma'am.
It was foolishness.
Look, I did a lot of bad
things back in the day
and that was just the one
they caught me for.
This is God's plan.
- "Here it is. I found it."
- "Good, good, good, good. Okay."
- "Hold it up."
- "Dad."
"No, come on. Hold it up.
Higher, higher, higher. Okay."
"It's just a town hall report."
"No, it's your first
newspaper article..."
She was a good girl.
A fine human being.
We're sorry for your loss,
Mr. Mitchell.
Thank you.
Would you mind terribly if I
just took a little look around?
Uh, no, uh, not at all.
The kitchen is, uh, there,
and her office is this way.
These...
Are her notebooks.
She kept good notes.
I taught her that.
I apologized to her only last week
teaching her a dying profession.
Journalism's dying, you know.
All this...
Internet.
Uh, maybe we should go
in the living room, Mr. Mitchell.
- Uh, yeah.
- I'll take this.
I'll be right there.
Just try and relax, sir.
Can I get you something to drink,
Mr. Mitchell?
Some water, maybe?
Yeah. That would be very nice,
thank you.
"It's newspaper articles."
"No, I've been published
in real newspapers before."
- "Those were not real newspapers."
- "Yes, they were so!"
"No, they weren't.
No, okay. All right, all right."
"Now I want you to read from it."
- "Come on. Read from it."
- "I'm reading it."
"Out loud! Go on!"
"Grove Park interim
mayor Joyce Franklin"
"presided today over the opening
of a brand-new senior center"
"named for retiring
councilman Sam Chapin."
"Uh... there."
"Read the whole thing. Come on."
"The center will serve
the Grove Park community"
"and the surrounding areas..."
Jane! Jane! Get in here!
Heart attack. Ambulance.
Mr. Mitchell, stay with me.
Thanks.
"Flacco is continuing
to pummel Merriman..."
The doctors say Tom Mitchell
had a major cardiac arrest.
I could have told them that.
They were able to stabilize him,
but he's still unconscious.
They're gonna keep him in I.C.U.
until he wakes up.
Poor man.
- Went down and stayed down.
- Oh, yeah.
But I've been looking through
Mitchell's notebooks.
Aside from a whole bunch
of stuff about the dangers
of mixed martial arts
fighting and blood markers
she was looking
for a fight fixing angle.
- What do you think?
- Merriman took a fall?
Ah, I can't see it.
It's worth killing over, though.
A lot of money to be made
on a sure thing.
We should talk to the promoter,
Artash
see what he has to say
about fight fixing.
Mr. Artash?
All right, 60/40 split.
And an option
for his next three fights.
Hey, alternatively,
go eat a shoelace.
Hey. I want the deal done by Friday.
Call me back.
We got it!
Manny fights for the title,
six months' time.
$2 million purse.
Can I pick 'em or what?
You see that kid
with the long hair?
He's gonna be my next champion.
Mark my words.
Fight fixing...
What can you tell us about it?
No, that doesn't happen.
The board finds out everyone involved
is done forever.
And you need a fighter
willing to take a dive
- which Merriman isn't.
- No?
Egotistical jerk like him?
Come on!
Stick the jab and shoot it.
Stick and shoot!
Get off the ropes!
Your fighter looks
bigger and stronger.
- Shouldn't he be winning?
- He's slower and dumber.
You're Floyd Benton, aren't you?
Didn't you train Manny Flacco?
Used to, until he got too big
and smart to learn.
Come on, son of a bitch.
Stick it! Move! Come on!
Police officer.
How'd you know?
Police and fine women always
think they got a right
to be wherever they're at,
and you ain't no fine woman.
I'm here about Charlotte Mitchell.
Yeah. Poor girl.
You think it was about the fight?
What do you think?
I think if it wasn't about the fight
you wouldn't even be here.
What aspect of the fight do you
think would motivate murder?
You're the detective.
What, am I supposed to do
your job for you?
What if I do your job for you?
Is that a fair exchange?
Shoot.
Artash's prospect has a tell.
He taps his forehead before
he throws a right uppercut.
When he does that, your guy should
step to the right and throw a hook.
Damn, if you ain't almost correct.
You got a good eye.
Well, thank you.
Now it's your turn.
Charlotte Mitchell...
Who killed her?
Don't know. But I will say this.
There's more to Manny Flacco
than meets the eye.
- And what's that?
- Just a vibe I get.
Does that vibe have anything to do
with the fact that he fired you
as his trainer?
I'm a bigger man than that.
Okay, listen up. Come here.
Come here, come here, come here.
Listen, the man there...
There she is...
Joe Reyes' old girlfriend.
Keep on going.
All right. Come on now.
- Keep movin'.
- Dawn May?
- We need to talk.
- What's this about?
You remember a guy
named Joe Reyes?
We need to know what happened
to a gun he gave you.
Could you guys keep it down?
People around here might get upset
they knew about my past business.
The gun...
What'd you do with it?
I gave it to my cousin Bobby.
I don't know what he did with it.
Where's your cousin Bobby?
Dead. Got blown up in Iraq.
- Excuse me.
- What's this all about?
- Hello?
- Am I in trouble?
Agent Rigsby,
this is J.J. LaRoche.
Where are you?
We need to talk more.
- I'm working a case.
- "When are you coming back in?"
Well, I couldn't say.
It's an active case.
I could agent Lisbon
to bring you back.
"Should I do that?"
I'll be there in an hour.
Two kids I'm trying to raise right
who don't know
the kind of life I used to lead.
Ma'am, we won't speak to your children
about this, unless we need to.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Thank you, ma'am. We'll be in touch.
- Thank you.
Says she was at a parent-teacher
conference the night before last.
Should be easy to check.
- Anything wrong? Who called?
- Nothing. Nobody.
You said there had
been no contact.
But phone records show six
phone calls from your father
between June and July of 2008.
What does this have to do with someone
burning a cop killer to death
here in CBI?
Nothing... directly.
- But it does speak to character.
- You're questioning my character?
Did you know there are criminological studies
that posit criminality as a heritable trait?
Like eye color
or a baritone voice.
What?
I just mean... it may not
be your fault, agent Rigsby.
You may simply be predisposed
to criminal behavior
scientifically speaking.
Look, my father called me
about a mix-up with his parole officer.
Was I supposed to
ignore him? Hang up?
And did you forget that conversation
or you just chose not to speak of it?
I forgot.
Are we done here?
I think we're done.
Hey. I got something.
A security guard had a run-in
with Charlotte Mitchell before the fight.
She was trying
to get into the dressing room area.
Didn't have the right kind of access laminate
so he wouldn't let her in.
She got agitated, made a scene
and he threw her out.
- This was at approximately 6:30.
- 6:30?
And that puts her in the arena an hour
before the M.E.'s estimate.
Yep, and that means Flacco and Merriman
both had opportunity.
They're suspects, too.
Bring 'em both in. See what they
have to say under questioning.
Okay.
Mr. Merriman, your associates
are gonna have to wait outside.
- Oh, they're cool.
- They're cool outside.
Hey, Flacco, you little punk!
You used plaster wraps, didn't you?
I know a little punk like
you don't hit that hard!
Mr. and Mrs. Flacco,
why don't we talk in my office?
Come on, babe.
Oh, now you running away, Manny?
Just like you did in the cage, huh?
Two million people saw me
kick your butt.
- Live with it.
- Oh, hell, no. Come on!
Control yourselves, both of you.
Look, either of you try anything
and I'm gonna put you in cuffs.
So let's just calm down
and get back to business.
I think you like
getting beaten up.
A little masochistic
streak there, huh?
Thanks for that. Thanks.
- Break it up, guys! That is enough!
- Hey! Take it easy, take it easy.
Come on! Knock it off!
Knock it off!
What the hell is going on here?
Do you people even
know what you're doing?
- Sit down, Mr. Lima.
- No!
Not until you tell me why you're setting
Manny up to get jumped.
Mr. Lima, how we conduct interviews
is not your concern.
It is if it endangers my fighter.
Manny shouldn't have been
called in here anyway.
He's grieving for Charlotte.
We just need to ask him
a few questions.
- Now, please, take a seat.
- Why?
I mean, you got the man
you want already.
- You mean Rowdy Merriman?
- You saw him.
He doesn't like it
when he doesn't get what he wants
and he didn't get what
he wanted from Charlotte.
- And what did he want?
- Guess.
Nah, I didn't kill the writer lady.
Why would I?
I've looked at your rap sheet.
There's a history of violence
against women.
Man, if I slap a bitch,
it's cause she asked for it.
Bitches like to get slapped.
Don't ask me why.
- Did Charlotte Mitchell ask for it?
- No, she didn't.
But I asked her, though, you know?
You know, she was like... "Ew!"
You know, I disgusted her, man.
Nice, clean, college lady.
She rejected you.
How'd that make you feel?
Like I had to call another bitch
to break me off a piece, which I did.
Now she was researching
you and Flacco.
Maybe she found out
something about you
you didn't want anybody to know.
Man, you know what?
I got nothin' to hide.
I'm straight up thug,
and I'm proud of it.
You know, what they gonna say about me
that ain't already been said, huh?
Nah. Little Mr. Perfect...
He's the one got secrets to be hidin'.
Flacco... What's he got to hide?
I mean, he was knocking boots
with that writer lady, for one
- dogging on that nasty little wife of his.
- You got proof of that?
Proof, man. Ask the punk, dude.
He'll be like...
Yeah, go ask him.
Mr. Flacco?
Do you want your wife present
during our interview?
Normally, we do this alone.
I need her here.
I got no secrets from Bea.
Okay. What was your relationship
with Charlotte Mitchell?
She was writing a book about
me and Rowdy, about the fight.
- Which started when?
- Since I started training for the fight.
Six months ago.
And how about
when you weren't training?
- What does that mean?
- Don't act dumb, Manny.
She wants to know if you were
sleeping with her.
- What? No.
- Look at me when you say that.
- Honey, I wasn't sleeping with her.
- "Honey"? Please.
- So he's sleeping with her? So what?
- Bea...
No. I don't wanna hear it now.
We've been together since I'm 13
married since 17, 4 kids.
You think I don't know
what's going on?
He's a professional athlete.
I blame it on the women.
Men don't know any better.
- Baby, I never s...
- And you know what?
Manny's good.
He doesn't go all crazy.
But we do have the nurse
at the physio clinic
the two waitresses in Vegas,
the girl at Len's club...
Where were you the night
of the fight, Ms. Flacco?
Backstage.
I... I can't take it
when Manny's fighting.
I wait until it's over.
Was anybody with you?
Yes. Plenty of people.
There's always people around.
But yeah, you know what?
I could have sneaked off
and killed the lady...
Only I didn't.
We done?
For now.
- Bea, come on.
- No, no, no.
- Don't be mad.
- Not here.
You wanna talk to Floyd Benton.
The lady was gonna write
about how he dopes
his young fighters at his gym.
That's why we took
Manny out of there.
Where were you the night
of the Flacco/Merriman fight?
At the fight. I had to buy a ticket.
You believe that?
Charlotte Mitchell asked you about steroid
use at your gym, correct?
Beatriz Flacco.
She hasn't liked me since
she was a little girl in pigtails.
What's Beatriz Flacco
got to do with this?
- She told you that crap.
- We heard from numerous sources
that Flacco fired you as his trainer
because you were pushing
steroids on him.
- No one was pushed to do anything.
- But there was steroid abuse
and Charlotte found out
about it, right?
Big scoop. Athletes get juiced.
Steroid abuse is a crime.
So arrest me. I won't resist.
I've done far worse things
than abuse steroids.
I wouldn't hurt a lady over
some picayune nonsense like...
Steroids? Please.
They all had motive,
and they all had opportunity.
What about the notebooks?
I read her last six months of notes.
- There's nothing useful that I could see.
- Could I take a look?
Be my guest.
- Excuse me, agent.
- Mr. Reyes, what brings you here?
Look, I just saw on TV
that that lady who died...
Her father just had
a heart attack.
- Now is he gonna be okay?
- I'm not sure yet. He's in I.C.U.
What's up, Mr. Reyes?
Look, I lied before.
Take a seat.
Thanks.
Go ahead.
When I told you I don't
see Dawn anymore
well, I... I do... see her every
now and again.
- You know, for old times' sake.
- Hey, why not?
You people got me thinking
about that damn gun
and all the mess it's caused,
so I went to see Dawn
and she told me she told
you she gave that gun
to her cousin Bobby, who passed.
That's right. We can't track
the gun past him.
Yeah, well, it's not true
what she said.
She didn't gave that gun to Bobby,
God rest his soul.
She just said that because Bobby's dead
and he can't deny it, you know?
- She didn't wanna get into trouble.
- What did she do with the gun?
Frank Lopez. We need to talk to you.
CBI? I ain't never been
questioned by the CBI.
Guys...
Thank you.
What you got?
Ten years ago,
a woman named Dawn May
- gave you a 9-millimeter handgun.
- She did?
- You still have the weapon?
- Why do you ask?
Well, the gun was used
in a murder two days ago.
Oops.
Dawn May.
The name's not ringing any bells.
What kind of gun was it?
9-millimeter.
Oh, yeah! Yeah,
it was a nice weapon. A Glock.
Yeah, Dawn.
Skinny, crazy girl.
What happened to Dawn?
Oh, she's fine.
And the Glock?
- Oh, I lost it.
- You lost it.
Yeah. Four years ago...
At a club called, uh...
Narcissus. You know it?
There was a scuffle.
I had to run out after some punk.
Next time I look, the 9 was gone.
It's a nice weapon,
but what can you do?
And, uh, where were you
two nights ago?
I was here.
Any one of these guys will tell you.
You don't believe me?
You can lie-detect me.
I ain't worried.
What'd you get?
That guy LaRoche... He wants
to talk to me wants me to come in.
What'd he talk to you about?
Okay, look, uh,
I have to tell you something.
I should've told
you before, but I didn't.
Two years ago, my dad called me
and he was getting hit
with a parole violation.
Seen consorting
with known criminals
and he was looking at a full
20-year bit in Folsom.
- So you alibied him out.
- Yeah.
I said he was with me
at the time, but...
I'm family.
So the parole officer wanted to know
if there was anybody else there
you know, who could verify it,
and... I said you.
- What?
- It just came out of my mouth.
I swear to God, if I could've taken it back,
I would've.
But they never checked
back with you
and everything seemed fine,
so I just forgot about it
until LaRoche started
questioning me.
So you involved me in your perjury
and now P.S.U. is investigating it.
If LaRoche finds out about this,
my career is over.
Yeah, it is, unless I lie as well
back you up, right?
Look, I'm sorry, man.
I know I've put you in a bad spot.
I've been a cop close to ten years.
Never lied to another cop,
not once.
Look, I'm not asking
for you to lie now.
I just... I want you to do
what you think is right.
Yeah.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm not lying for you.
"Manny Flacco will be fighting"
"for the middleweight crown
on Cinco de Mayo."
"It will be a second
American revolution."
"What a country."
"Where else can a kid
from the barrio"
"and a son of Armenian immigrants"
"come together to make something
like this happen?"
"Me, a guy, who five years ago,
owned a few parking lots"
"and a couple of restaurants
and nightclubs?"
"And a kid who never graduated
high school."
"But we had a dream, and today
that dream is a reality.
"God bless America."
- Anything on Mitchell's notes?
- Not a thing.
Manny Flacco is challenging
for the middleweight crown.
- Len Artash just announced it.
- What are you doing?
Going to talk to Len Artash.
You coming?
Pull the guard!
Reverse, reverse, reverse.
- Watch the guillotine!
- Artash, got some questions for you.
- You were born in America, yes?
- That's right.
- And your parents are Armenian.
- Yes. Why?
- What was your father's name?
- Arik Artashian.
- What's your father's name?
- Floyd.
And your mother?
Nancy. What is this about?
Nancy... doesn't sound
like an Armenian name.
No, it's not. It's what she called herself
when she got here to America.
- What was she christened?
- Nargiz.
- And do you have...
- I bet that means something beautiful.
- It's a flower.
Either of you recognize this?
No. What is it?
It's Charlotte
Mitchell's notebook.
You know what that says?
- What about you?
- No.
- What do you think it is?
- I don't know.
Some kind of coded shorthand,
most likely.
Doesn't matter. I'll bet her father
knows what it says.
Doctors said that Thomas Mitchell
has taken a turn for the better.
Expected to regain consciousness
in 12 to 24 hours, right?
- Right.
- Right, so there we have it.
Thomas Mitchell will tell us
what this says
and then I'll bet we will find out what
Charlotte learned that got her killed.
I went through that entire notebook.
There wasn't any shorthand in it.
Really? How weird.
Wonder where it came from.
You served in the military
didn't you, agent Cho?
Yes.
- Rangers?
- Special Forces.
So... you understand
the concept of honor.
That's an affidavit
that Wayne Rigsby signed
saying that you and he spent
an afternoon
with his criminal father.
You remember that day, agent Cho?
Agent Rigsby initially claimed
to have no contact with his father
then became evasive when confronted
with his falsehood.
Looking into it,
I... discovered that...
Wayne provided an alibi
that kept his father out of jail...
And you were part of that alibi.
So...
I just need you to confirm...
On your honor...
That you were indeed
there that day.
Yes, I was.
I was there with agent Rigsby
and his father.
Okay.
Good.
What did you do that afternoon...
The three of you?
Give me some details.
I don't recall.
Nothing at all?
Strange.
I was there.
I'll swear to it.
You need me to sign something
to make it official?
No.
That won't be necessary.
That'll be all. Thank you, agent.
I told him I was with you.
All right, let's go.
We've gotta get to the hospital.
Jane and Van Pelt are already there.
You guys okay?
Let's go. I'll explain on the way.
All clear in Mitchell's room.
Hallway's clear.
All clear here.
Wait a minute.
I think I saw Reyes.
He's headed your way.
I see him, Cho.
Cut him off.
Mr. Reyes.
What are you doing here?
Um, I was just coming
to pay my respects.
No, you can't be here.
We have to leave now.
Wait. I didn't mean anything.
What are you doing?
Don't argue, Mr. Reyes.
Right this way. Come on.
Mr. Lima, put your hands on
your head where I can see 'em.
Mr. Mitchell left the I.C.U. yesterday
but I'll be glad to pass
on your best wishes.
Whatever. You got nothing.
That notebook shorthand
crap won't fly in court.
True enough. I happened to write
that notebook shorthand crap myself.
Charlotte Mitchell was murdered
because she discovered a secret.
I simply had to convince the killer
that the secret didn't die with her.
Et voila.
And this should fly
nicely in court.
- You got it all wrong...
- Save it.
This is the gun that was used
to shoot Charlotte Mitchell
and you're the one who killed her.
You can have these back now,
Mr. Mitchell.
I, uh...
I'm sorry,
but I... I scribbled in one of those.
That's, uh, how we caught the man
that shot your daughter.
- I hope you don't mind.
- No, no. That's, uh...
So... um, it's over?
- You've solved the case?
- Yes.
Now we're just tying up
some loose ends.
Never... never would've figured
Suge Lima as a murderer.
Yeah, that's terrible.
- Shocking.
- Yes, it is.
What for? Why did he do it?
So, uh... is there anything
I can do to help?
There is, actually.
- Your... your mother's name... the flower?
- Yes. Nargiz.
Nargiz, which means...
Narcissus...
Same name as your club
named it after your mom.
- Yeah.
- Club Narcissus
where Frank Lopez
lost Joe Reyes' gun.
Yeah, the one
he got from Dawn May.
- That one.
- Who? What?
You don't know the guys,
but we know how you got the gun
that Lima used to kill Charlotte Mitchell
and you're under arrest. Stand up.
The only thing we don't know
is why you had to kill her.
And that's what we're gonna find out.
Mr. Flacco, do you remember
around a year ago
giving blood to be tested?
Sure. Results came back
said I was as healthy as a horse.
Suge told me.
Suge lied.
He and Artash
submitted the samples
under Suge's name instead
of yours just in case.
Markers showed
a high level of protein
that indicates cranial
bleeding and spinal leakage.
Oh, my God.
Charlotte Mitchell
figured out the switch.
I know that blood sample
was Manny's, not Lima's.
If Manny gets in that cage,
he could die.
What the hell are you
talking about, lady?
And how'd you get your hands
on those tests?
Stop the fight, Len, or else.
All right, all right.
I'll stop the fight. Calm down.
We got a problem.
Those sons of bitches.
They risked Manny's life.
No M.M.A. authority would let him
in the cage if word got out.
It's one doctor's opinion.
He looks fine to me.
Do you really think
you'll get away with this?
I will tell everyone.
Let go of me.
It's gonna be fine, baby.
We're gonna make it through this.
You gotta feel for the guy.
He lost his livelihood.
Lost a life of getting hit in the head
but he got his marriage back.
- Seems like a fair trade to me.
- Aren't you the romantic.
Makes the world go round.
Hey. Cho.
Thank you.